Guide to the Wayne P. Ellis Collection of Kodakiana, 1886-1989 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Periodicals Series, 1907-1985 and undated (Box 22)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 36)
    - Kodak (Box 36)
      Seems to be for employees. Contains information on policies relating to Kodak employees in the military, new Kodak military teaching films, excerpts from speeches by Lincoln.
      - 21:2 (Feb. 1942)- excerpt (Box 36)
    - Kodak Bulletin for the Graphic Arts (Box 36)
      For professional photographers. Contains articles based on technical memoranda or convention papers, on professional topics (halftones, duotones, posterized negatives, mechanized film processing, etc.). Also offers information on Kodak products and articles on their use, with many illustrative photographs.
      - 2-6 (undated), 8-9 (undated), 13 (1968), 15 (1968), 17 (1969), 19 (undated) (Box 36)
    - Kodak Camera Club News (Box 36)
      For amateurs and the general public. Contains picture-taking tips (taking photographic membership cards, creative still-lifes or reflections, etc.), information on new Kodak books and products, and information on specific camera clubs (e.g., Toronto Camera Club). Issues lack volume numbers and other issue identifiers.
      - [cover with sunlight effect], [circa 1970], [cover with child's face], [ca. 1975] (Box 36)
    - Kodak Dealer-Finisher News (Box 36)
      For professional sales staff. Contains advance information on the new Kodak Instamatic Camera and Kodapak Film Cartridges, with parts breakdown, selling-point highlights, reasoning behind the products, promotional signs to purchase, and questions and answers about the products.
      - April 1963 (Box 36)
    - Kodak International Photography (Box 36)
      For professional photographers. Contents include photographs from professional international photographers; essays on specific photographers; and articles on photographic exhibits, types of commercial photography (record jackets), and types of camera.
      - 10 (1974) (Box 36)
    - Kodak Magazine for the Graphics Professional (Box 36)
      For professional photographers. Contains informational articles on photography (halftones, phototypesetting, etc.), and information on Kodak products, trade shows, etc.
      - 3 (1985) (Box 36)
    - Kodak News (by 1954 entitled Kodak Dealer News) (Box 36)
      For professional sales staff. Contains advance notice of new Kodak products; information on promotional items, contests, displays; and sales ideas (TV ads, showing related accessories, etc.).
      - 35:8 (Aug. 1949), 35:12 (Dec. 1949), 40:5-7 (June/July-Oct. 1954), 41:3-4 (Mar.-May 1955) (Box 36)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 37)
    - Kodak Photo (Box 37)
      For amateur photographers. Contains educational articles on photography (primarily color photography) in non-technical language; advertisements for Kodak products; many illustrative photographs; and section with suggestions for individuals about submitted photographs.
      - 1:1 (1946) (Box 37)
    - Kodak Photo Magazine (Box 37)
      For amateur photographers. Contains many articles on photography (mounting in albums, seasonal photography, series shots, indoor v. outdoor lighting, etc.); many illustrative photographs; information about new Kodak products; and "Good Shots" section with amateur photographs.
      - Fall 1946, Holiday 1946, Feb./Mar. 1947, Fall 1947 (Box 37)
    - Kodak Photo News (Box 37)
      For amateurs. Contains primarily detailed information on new Kodak products and shows (including "Profile '76," a multimedia show focusing on people across the country for the bicentennial), also "Tear-Out Tips" on photography.
      - 1975:2-3, 1976:1, 1976:3, 1983:1, 1985:1 (Box 37)
    - Kodak Trade Circular (Box 37)
      For professional sales personnel, labeled "Confidential-For Trade Circulation Only-Read and file for future reference." Contains information on new and discontinued Kodak products, price changes, advance information about Kodak ads and promotions, display window and sales suggestions.
      - 24:4 (Apr. 1923), Index for 30 (Jan.-Dec. 1929), 39:1 (Jan. 1938), 39:10 (Oct. 1938), 42:1 (Jan. 1941), 43:11-12 (Nov.-Dec. 1942) (Box 37)
    - New England Photographer (Box 37)
      For professional photographers. Contains professional articles (doretype processing, darkroom efficiency, fluorescent lighting), many advertisements for Kodak products, and commercial articles (training apprentices, boosting business. etc/)
      - 19:3 (Jan./Feb. 1941) (Box 37)
    - The Photo Finisher (Box 37)
      For professional photographers (finishers). Contains advance information on new Kodak products, services, and promotions with ordering information; professional articles (hot weather finishing, copying photographs, coloring photos, etc.); and commercial articles ( advertising, keeping agents interested).
      - 3:3 (July 1929), 3:7 (Nov. 1929), 3:9 (Jan. 1930), 3:11 (Mar. 1930), 4:2 (June 1930), 5:1 (Jan. 1931), 5:7 (July 1931), 5:11 (Nov. 1931), 6:3 (Apr./May 1932), 7:2-3 (Mar.-Apr. 1934), 8:3 (Apr. 1935), 8:5 (June 1935), 9:1 (Jan. 1936), 10:3-5 (Apr.-Sept. 1937), 11:6 (Nov./Dec. 1938), 12:2 (Mar. 1939), 13:2 (Mar. 1940), 15:1 (Jan./Feb. 1942), 20:5 (Nov. 1948) (Box 37)
    - Photographic Review/Photographic Digest (Box 37)
      For professional photographers. Contains many ads for Kodak photographic products, information on conventions, commercial articles (national advertising, training apprentices, gift certificates), professional articles (hot weather fixing, focusing wide angle lenses), joke page entitled "Retouching Some Old Ones." Regionally published magazine with slightly differing cover design, but virtually identical contents. Titles vary with region.
      - Photographic Review: (Chicago, Ill.) (Box 37)
        - 4:12 (June 1926) (Box 37)
      - Photographic Review: (Jacksonville, Fla.) (Box 37)
        - [vol. page cut off] (June/July 1938) (Box 37)
      - Photographic Digest: (Philadelphia) (Box 37)
        - 6:4 (Oct. 1927), 8:7 (Jan. 1930), 9:6 (Dec. 1930), 9:11 (May 1931), 10:1 (July 1931), 11:7 (Jan. 1933), 11:10 (Apr. 1933) (Box 37)
      - Photographic Digest: (San Francisco) (Box 37)
        - 16:4 (Feb./Mar. 1938) (Box 37)
    - Tech Bits (Box 37)
      For professional scientists and engineers. Contains highlights of Kodak products and articles on photography topics (cleaning plates, washing photographic materials, making microscopic reticles, splicing films, etc.). Technical language used throughout and illustrated with many graphs.
      - 1963:3, 1964:1-4, 1965:2, 1966:1-4, 1968:2-3, 1969:1, 1969:4 (Box 37)
- Product Catalogs Series, 1890-1985 and undated (Box 37)
  Contains a variety of catalogs describing a wide array of photographic products. Audiences are both professional persons and the general public. Arranged chronologically within folders or boxes.
  - Kodak Product Catalogs Subseries, 1890-1985 and undated (Box 37)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 38)
      - Multi-product catalogs, 1890-1916, (26 items) (Box 38)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 39)
      - Multi-product catalogs, 1917-1931, (21 items) (Box 39)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 40)
      - Multi-product catalogs, 1932-1955, (34 items) (Box 40)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 41)
      - Multi-product catalogs (oversize), 1931, 1955, 1961, 1966, 1971-1973, undated, (9 items) (Box 41)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 42)
      - Cine-Kodak equipment catalogs (oversize), 1927-1941, 1946-1947, 1950, 1957, undated, (59 items) (Box 42)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 43)
      - Kodascope Library catalogs 1924-1938, (9 items) (Box 43)
      - Kodascope Library Review, undated, (2 items) (Box 43)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 44)
      - Kodak schools, teaching guides, contests, 1905-1980, (12 items) (Box 44)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 45)
      - Multi-product catalogs for graphic arts professionals (oversize), 1910-1985 and undated, (14 items) (Box 45)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 46)
      - Materials for the graphic arts (oversize), 1948-1967 and undated, (7 items) (Box 46)
      - Photographic products catalogs (oversize), 1977-1983 and undated, (4 items) (Box 46)
      - Kodak Products for the Professional (oversize), 1953-1974, (6 items) (Box 46)
  - Non-Kodak Product Catalogs Subseries, circa 1860-1972 and undated (Box 46)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 47)
      - Ansco, 1906-1918 and undated, (4 items) (Box 47)
      - E. and H. T. Anthony, [1860?]-1891, (3 items) (Box 47)
      - Blair Camera, 1895-1911, (10 items) (Box 47)
      - Borsum Camera, 1900 (Box 47)
      - Burke and Ames (Rexo Camera), undated (Box 47)
      - Calumet Photographic, [1970?], (4 items) (Box 47)
      - Camera Place, undated (Box 47)
      - Canadian Card Company, 1907, 1911, (2 items) (Box 47)
      - Central Camera, 1930-1938, (3 items) (Box 47)
      - Century Camera, 1901-1910, (4 items) (Box 47)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 48)
      - Commercial Camera Company (Photostat Camera), undated (Box 48)
      - Conley Camera Company (Kewpie Camera), undated (Box 48)
      - Dallmeyer, undated, (4 items) (Box 48)
      - Elko, 1942 (Box 48)
      - GAF Corporation, 1972, (2 items) (Box 48)
      - Gundalch Optical (Korona Camera), 1899-1915, (7 items) (Box 48)
      - Hasselblad, [1966?], undated, (2 items) (Box 48)
      - Horne, Thornwaite and Wood, 1890 (Box 48)
      - Ilex Optical, undated (Box 48)
      - International Photo Sales Company (Ipsco Camera), undated, (2 items) (Box 48)
      - Manhattan Optical, 1895-1900, (3 items) (Box 48)
      - Minox, undated (Box 48)
      - George Murphy, Inc., 1900-1932, (3 items) (Box 48)
      - Photo Printer Manufacturing Company, undated (Box 48)
      - James W. Queen and Company, 1892 (Box 48)
      - Ray Camera, 1898, 1900, (2 items) (Box 48)
      - Riley Brothers, 1896-1897 (Box 48)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 49)
      - Scovill Manufacturing Company, 1883 (Box 49)
      - Seneca Camera, 1904-1925, undated, (13 items) (Box 49)
      - Solar Cine Products, 1970-1972, (3 items) (Box 49)
      - Stirn and Lyon, reprint, undated (Box 49)
      - Sunart Photo, 1896 (Box 49)
      - Vives Camera Company, 1901 (Box 49)
      - Voigtlander, [1906?]-[1910?], undated, (7 items) (Box 49)
      - Wollensak Optical, 1919, undated, (2 items) (Box 49)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 50)
      - American Optical (oversized), [1946?] (Box 50)
      - E. and H. T. Anthony (oversized), 1896 (Box 50)
      - Bausch and Lomb Optical (oversized), 1913 (Box 50)
      - Bell and Howell (Filmo Camera, oversized), 1939 (Box 50)
      - Burke and James (oversized), 1969 (Box 50)
      - Calumet Manufacturing (oversized), 1966 (Box 50)
      - Central Camera Company (oversized), undated (Box 50)
      - Century Camera (oversized, plus close-ups of cover), 1905, (2 items) (Box 50)
      - Graflex (oversized), 1967, undated, (7 items) (Box 50)
      - Andrew Lloyd and Company (oversized), [1901?] (Box 50)
      - Montgomery Ward (oversized), 1898-1952, (3 items) (Box 50)
      - Photo-Porst (oversized), [ca. 1937] (Box 50)
      - Rieztschel (oversized), 1909, undated, (2 items) (Box 50)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 51)
      - Premo (Rochester Optical Company) catalogs, 1890-1909, (26 items) (Box 51)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 52)
      - Premo catalogs, 1910-1922, (18 items) (Box 52)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 53)
      - Graflex ( Folmer and Schwing Division of Kodak), 1907-1929, 1935, 1940, 1956, 1967, and undated, (30 items) (Box 53)
- Kodak Products Leaflets Series, 1912-1989 and undated (Box 53)
  Ephemeral publications promoting a variety of Kodak products, including cameras, lenses, photographic papers and films, darkroom equipment, and photography albums. Arranged by date within folders.
  - Contents of Box: (Box 54)
    - Kodak Instamatic, 1963, 1969, 1974, (3 items) (Box 54)
    - Kodak Signet 40, 1953, 1956, (4 items) (Box 54)
    - Kodak Retina Cameras, 1955, 1957, (3 items) (Box 54)
    - Kodak Medalist and Medalist II, 1941, 1947, 1949, (3 items) (Box 54)
    - Kodak Bantam Special, 1931, 1936, (3 items) (Box 54)
    - Continental Kodaks, 1930, undated, (2 items) (Box 54)
    - Kodak Ektra, undated (Box 54)
    - Super Kodak Six-20, undated (Box 54)
    - Kodak Brownie Cameras, 1958, 1962, (2 items) (Box 54)
    - Kodak Stereo Camera, 1957, (2 items) (Box 54)
    - Kodak Miniature Cameras, 1938, 1940, 1941, 1955, undated, (5 items) (Box 54)
    - Kodak Reflex, 1946 (Box 54)
    - Kodak Tourist Cameras, 1949 (Box 54)
    - Kodak 35mm Cameras, 1957 (Box 54)
    - Kodak Movie Cameras, 1960, 1973, undated, (3 items) (Box 54)
    - Kodachrome, 1936, 1938, 1939, 1964, (4 items) (Box 54)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 55)
    - Eastman Professional Films, 1918, 1928, 1931-1933, 1936-1938, undated, (10 items) (Box 55)
    - Kodak Films, 1936, 1938, 1939, 1949, undated, (5 items) (Box 55)
    - Vitava Portrait Papers, 1925, 1930, undated, (4 items) (Box 55)
    - Eastman Plates, 1924, 1930, 1935-1938, undated, (8 items) (Box 55)
    - Eastman Photographic Papers, 1935 (Box 55)
    - Velox Papers, 1912, 1915, 1922, 1928, 1934, undated, (7 items) (Box 55)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 56)
    - Eastman Professional Films, Plates and Papers, 1938, 1940, 1942, undated, (8 items) (Box 56)
    - Kodak Movie Projectors, 1941, 1953, 1954, 1964, 1936, undated, (6 items) (Box 56)
    - Kodak Slide Projectors, 1937, 1947-1950, 1952, 1954-1956, (11 items) (Box 56)
    - Kodak Filters, 1938, 1940, 1946-1947, 1954, (6 items) (Box 56)
    - Lens Attachments, undated, (2 items) (Box 56)
    - Kodak Albums, 1948 (Box 56)
    - Kodak Enlarging Equipment, 1941-1942, 1945, 1948-1950, undated, (10 items) (Box 56)
    - Kodak Pola-Lights, 1949 (Box 56)
    - Kodak Darkroom Equipment, 1947-1948, undated, (4 items) (Box 56)
    - Kodak Accessories, 1951, 1964, (2 items) (Box 56)
    - Eastman X-Ray Materials and Accessories, 1922 (Box 56)
    - Kodak Programs for Home Viewing, 1979, 1989, undated, (3 items) (Box 56)
    - Guide to Kodak How-To Books, 1974 (Box 56)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 57)
    - Kodachrome and Kodacolor from All Angles (book), 1942 (Box 57)
    - Kodachrome and Ektachrome from All Angles (book), 1949 (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous oversized leaflets, 1948, 1950, 1959, 1966, 1984, (5 items) (Box 57)
- Photography Manuals Series, [circa 1890]-1987 and undated (Box 57)
  Pamphlets, bound volumes, and audio-visual publications aimed chiefly at amateur photographers, although some are also directed at professionals. Includes both general reference works and works relating to specific photographic techniques such as flash photography and portraits. Many of these publications are connected with specific equipment. Arranged in chronological order within folders or boxes.
  - Amateur/General Public Subseries, 1898-1987 and undated (Box 57)
    - General Topics (Box 57)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 58)
        - How to Make Good Pictures, 1912, 1928, 1935-1940, (7 items) (Box 58)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 59)
        - How to Make Good Pictures, 1941, 1943, (6 items) (Box 59)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 60)
        - How to Make Good Pictures, 1951-1952, 1957, 1967, 1972, 1981, (6 items) (Box 60)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 61)
        - How to Make Good Pictures, undated, (6 items) (includes one copy in Spanish) (Box 61)
        - Picture Taking and Picture Making, 1898 (5th and 7th editions), (2 items) (Box 61)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 62)
        - Picture Taking and Picture Making, 1898 (8th and 11th editions), (2 items) (Box 62)
        - How to Make Good Movies, [1953?], (2 items) (Box 62)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 63)
        - How to Make Good Home Movies, 1958-1966, (3 items) (Box 63)
        - Junior Scenarios for Home Movies, 1928 (Box 63)
        - Home Movies Made Easy, 1970 (Box 63)
        - How to Make Good Sound Movies, 1973 (Box 63)
        - Better Movies in Minutes, 1972 (Box 63)
        - Maintaining Your Still and Movie Camera and Projector, 1975 (Box 63)
        - Kodak Pocket Guide to Video, 1987 (Box 63)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 64)
        - The Modern Way in Picture Making, 1905, 1907 (Box 64)
        - The Fundamentals of Photography, 1928 (Box 64)
        - At Home with Your Kodak, [1935?] (Box 64)
        - The Modern Kodak - How to Make the Most of It, [1928?], (4 items) (Box 64)
        - Photography, 1937, 1942, (2 folders) (Box 64)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 65)
        - The Way to Better Pictures, undated (Box 65)
        - Photography Simplified, 1938 (Box 65)
        - Photography in Wartime, 1944 (Box 65)
        - What to Photograph, 1945 (Box 65)
        - X-Rays and You, 1948 (Box 65)
        - Photo Tips, 1950 (Box 65)
        - The Kodak Camera Guide, 1959 (Box 65)
        - The Here's How Book of Photography, 1971 (Box 65)
        - The Here's How Book of Photography, vol. 2, 1977 (Box 65)
        - Kodak Master Photoguide, 1981 (Box 65)
        - Kodak Pocket Guide to Great Picture Taking, 1984 (Box 65)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 66)
        - Kodak Reference Handbook, 1940-1949, [1943?], 1948, (3 items) (Box 66)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 67)
        - Kodak Photographic Handbook, [1952?], [1964?], [1973?], (3 items) (Box 67)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 68)
        - Kodak Information Book, 1943 (Box 68)
        - The Joy of Photography, 1979 (Box 68)
        - More Joy of Photography, 1981 (Box 68)
        - What You Can do With a Kodak, undated (Box 68)
    - Specific Topics (Box 68)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 69)
        - About Lenses, 1921-1922, 1923, 1925, (4 items) (Box 69)
        - Artura Results, undated, 8th, 9th, 17th, 19th eds., (4 items) (Box 69)
        - Cine-Kodak, 1923-1924, 1928, 1931-1932, 1936, 1946, undated, (15 items) (Box 69)
        - Kodak Films, 1947, 1952-1954, 1956, 1975, 1978, (8 items) (Box 69)
        - Seed Plates, undated (Box 69)
        - Slide Showmanship with a Kodak Carousel Projector, 1975 (Box 69)
        - Kodak Filters, 1956 (Box 69)
        - Picture Taking at Night, 1935 (Box 69)
        - Let's Take Kodacolor Pictures, 1952 (Box 69)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 70)
        - Enlarging, 1897, 1910, 1915, 1921-1922, 1924, 1926, 1934-1935, 1952, (10 items) (Box 70)
        - Kodascope, 1926-1927, 1929, 1932, 1934, 1937, 1945, (7 items) (Box 70)
        - Brownie Hawkeye Camera, 1952-1955, (4 items) (Box 70)
        - Kodak Duraflex II and III, 1952-1954, (5 items) (Box 70)
        - An Amateur Photoplay in the Making, [ca. 1927] (Box 70)
        - Flash Photography, 1915, 1917, 1965, (3 items) (Box 70)
        - Picture Taking with Still Cameras, 1948 (Box 70)
        - Better Snapshots of Your Children, 1954 (Box 70)
        - Travel Pictures, 1963 (Box 70)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 71)
        - The Photography of Colored Objects, 1923, 1928, 1938, (3 items) (Box 71)
        - Kodak Guide to 35mm Photography, 1986 (Box 71)
        - Photography by Polarized Light, 1938 (Box 71)
        - How to Make Ten Dollars a Day with Your Kodak, 1926 (Box 71)
        - Adventures in Existing-Light Photography, 1978 (Box 71)
        - Kodak Pocket Guide to Sports Photography, 1984 (Box 71)
        - Minitography and Cinetography, 1931 (Box 71)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 72)
        - The Kodak Manual for No. 4 Folding Kodak, 1891 (Box 72)
        - Printing, Developing and Enlarging, 1947-1948, 1982, (3 items) (Box 72)
        - Graphic Graflex Photography, 1944 (Box 72)
        - Picturing the Times of Your Life, 1980 (Box 72)
        - Picturing People, 1976 (Box 72)
        - The Joy of Photographing People, 1983 (Box 72)
    - Non-Kodak Product Manuals (Box 72)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 73)
        - Agfa/Ansco, 1943-1958, undated, (9 items) (Box 73)
        - Argus, 1954, undated, (3 items) (Box 73)
        - Bausch and Lomb, undated (Box 73)
        - DuPont Film, undated (Box 73)
        - Federal Manufacturing and Engineering Company, 1948 (Box 73)
        - Flashlight Portraiture, 1912 (Box 73)
        - General Electric, [1939?] (Box 73)
        - Kalart Company, 1955 (Box 73)
        - Medo Photo Supply, undated (Box 73)
        - Sears, Roebuck and Company, undated, (4 items) (Box 73)
        - Sylvania Electric, 1954-1966, (3 items) (Box 73)
        - Practical Photography, 1919, 1923, (2 items) (Box 73)
        - Photography Outdoors, 1911 (Box 73)
        - The New Photo-Miniature, [ca. 1890] (Box 73)
    - Audio-Visual Product Manuals (Kodak) (Box 73)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 74)
        - How to Process Color Negatives (audiocassette), 1975 (Box 74)
        - How to Process Black and White Films and Prints (audiocassette), 1975 (Box 74)
        - How to Process Color Prints (audiocassette), 1977 (Box 74)
        - Introduction to Photography (videotape 101), 1985 (Box 74)
        - Basic Picture-Taking (videotape 102), 1985 (Box 74)
        - The Art of Photo Composition (videotape 103), 1985 (Box 74)
        - Effective Use of Lenses (videotape 104), 1985 (Box 74)
      - Contents of Box: (Box 75)
        - Existing-Light Photography (videotape 105), 1985 (Box 75)
        - Photographers and Their Films (videotape 108), 1985 (Box 75)
        - Prize-Winning Pictures (videotape 110), 1985 (Box 75)
        - Action Photography (videotape 112), 1985 (Box 75)
        - Advanced Existing-Light Photography (videotape 113), 1985 (Box 75)
        - Scenic Photography (videotape 115), 1985 (Box 75)
        - The Way I See It (videotape 116), 1985 (Box 75)
        - Images with Imagination (videotape 123), 1985 (Box 75)
        - Glamour Photography (videotape 124), 1985 (Box 75)
        - Creating the Print (videotape 502), 1987 (Box 75)
  - Trade and Technical Subseries(some non-Kodak) 1917-1980 and undated (Box 75)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 76)
      - From Dry Plates to Ektachrome Film, 1921 (Box 76)
      - The Silver Bromide Grain of Photographic Emulsions, 1921 (Box 76)
      - Gelatin in Photography, 1923 (Box 76)
      - The Physics of the Developed Photographic Image, 1924 (Box 76)
      - Motion Picture Laboratory Practice, 1936 (Box 76)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 77)
      - Photographic Sensitometry, 1934 (Box 77)
      - Photomicrography, 1944 (Box 77)
      - Photographic Chemistry, 1980 (Box 77)
      - Commercial Photo and Amateur Finishing, 1924?-1925?, 1935, 1938, (4 items) (Box 77)
      - Films, Plates and Papers for Commercial Photography, 1920, 1923, 1927, 1930, 1934-1935, 1937-1938, (8 items) (Box 77)
      - Color Printing with Wash-Off Relief Film, 1938-1939, (2 items) (Box 77)
      - Kodak Lenses for Professional Photography, 1951 (Box 77)
      - Cinematographer's Field Guide, 1978 (Box 77)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 78)
      - Book of Formulas for Professional Films and Plates, 1932-1934, 1937-1938, (5 items) (Box 78)
      - Kodacolor Portraiture, undated (Box 78)
      - X-Rays, 1922, 1924, 1929, 1933, 1936, (5 items) (Box 78)
      - Motion Picture Films, 1931, 1935, 1938-1939, 1942, 1945, 1947, (8 items) (Box 78)
      - Lantern Slides, 1919, 1927, (4 items) (Box 78)
      - Collodion and the Making of Wet Plate Negatives, 1929 (Box 78)
      - Kodachrome Professional Film, 1941 (Box 78)
      - Making Service Pictures for Industry, 1952 (Box 78)
      - Photomicrography, 1932 (Box 78)
      - Professional Enlarging, 1917-1918, 1926, (3 items) (Box 78)
      - Advice for Photographic Studios, 1927, undated, (2 items) (Box 78)
      - Stains on Negatives and Prints, 1938 (Box 78)
      - Materials for the Construction of Photographic Processing Apparatus, 1929 (Box 78)
    - Contents of Box: (Box 79)
      - A Way to Do It Better, [196-] (Box 79)
      - Photo Topics and Techniques, 1980 (Box 79)
      - Clinical Photography, 1972 (Box 79)
      - Photography from Light Planes and Helicopters, 1971 (Box 79)
      - Ultraviolet and Fluorescence Photography, 1972 (Box 79)